<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on David Castillo</title>
    <link>https://davidcastilloalvarado.github.io/portfolio/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on David Castillo</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 21 Aug 2020 12:00:00 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://davidcastilloalvarado.github.io/portfolio/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Project 2: Titanic - ¿Who survived?</title>
      <link>https://davidcastilloalvarado.github.io/portfolio/post/project-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Aug 2020 08:58:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://davidcastilloalvarado.github.io/portfolio/post/project-2/</guid>
      <description>Context: Like a data scientist, i have made educational project to help myself and other to go deeply into data science popular tools and methods. In that way, this project has educational purpose, I will go through with EDA to response the principal questions over a tragedy like Titanic was, like what characterize to survivors or if the wealthiness is a factor. Also features engineer to fix the data missing o for create more features to better understand, and finally proceed with classification model that going to predict if a passenger survives basing of his features in the data set all this in the context of a Kaggel’s contend.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project 1: Sound Classification ESC10</title>
      <link>https://davidcastilloalvarado.github.io/portfolio/post/project-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Aug 2020 10:58:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://davidcastilloalvarado.github.io/portfolio/post/project-1/</guid>
      <description>Background: In this new era of automatization, we can make some process automatically, like recognize sound and get work on it, to deploy predictive maintenance or trigger alarms in machines. Like a rotatory machine, like rotors or bearings, o the bigger ones like hydro electric generators. So, this work is about that, classify sound into 10 different classes. I have implemented differents model and a benchmark of models to compare several algorithms to get which one is the best.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>